celebrityscandal.com 2018-05-13

# Celebrity Scandal - Privacy Policy

At celebrityscandal.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by celebrityscandal.com and how it is used. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

The following outlines our privacy policy. 

  * * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. 
  * * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 
  * * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 
  * * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. 
  * * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. 
  * * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 
  * * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. 

###  Log Files 

Like many other Web sites, celebrityscandal.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

###  Cookies and Web Beacons 

Celebrityscandal.com may use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on celebrityscandal.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

_Celebrityscandal.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers._

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. celebrityscandal.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
